<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>data quality on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/data-quality/</link><description>Recent content in data quality on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/data-quality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Quality Filter Matrix</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/dqfilters/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/dqfilters/</guid><description>name: dq_filters fullname: Data Quality Filter Matrix description: &amp;gt;This template summarizes the DDI Avg Weekly Percent (DDI) and Data Quality CoV (HasBeenE) (CoV (HasBeenE)) filters individually and in conjuction with one another. Original Code By: Kelly Carey. Adapted to the Rnssp Package by: Gbedegnon Roseric Azondekon. National Syndromic Surveillance Program (NSSP). Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). create_dir: true Detailed Description This template summarizes the Discharge Diagnosis Informative Avg Weekly Percent (DDI) and Data Quality Coefficient of Variation (CoV/CoV (HasBeenE)) filters individually and in conjuction with one another.</description></item><item><title>State Data Quality Report</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/statedqreport/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/statedqreport/</guid><description>name: state_dq_report fullname: State Data Quality Report description: &amp;gt;This template summarizes data quality metrics, including timeliness, completeness, and validity. It currently includes NSSP Priority 1 &amp;amp; NSSP Priority 2 elements. Original Code By: Andrew Farrey (Kentucky Injury Prevention and Research Center). Adapted to the Rnssp Package by: Gbedegnon Roseric Azondekon. National Syndromic Surveillance Program (NSSP). Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). create_dir: true Detailed Description The state data quality template calculates and summarizes syndromic surveillance data quality metrics pulled from the BioSense platform and the ESSENCE application programming interface (API) similar to the NSSP Data Quality Dashboards.</description></item></channel></rss>