<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lab on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/lab/</link><description>Recent content in lab on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/lab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lab Pathogen Surveillance</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/labpathogentrend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/labpathogentrend/</guid><description>name: lab_pathogen_trend fullname: Lab Pathogen Surveillance description: &amp;gt;Generates a report of all tests for a selected laboratory A laboratory category 2 pathogen by user selected time period and demographic stratification. Users can select to return the percent of tests with negative results or positive results. Original Code By: Jourdan Devies &amp;amp; Kelly Carey. Adapted to the Rnssp Package by: Gbedegnon Roseric Azondekon. National Syndromic Surveillance Program (NSSP). Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).</description></item><item><title>Lab Reason for Testing</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/labtestingreason/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/labtestingreason/</guid><description>name: lab_testing_reason fullname: Lab Reason for Testing description: &amp;gt;Summarizes the types of tests and patient demographics of a user defined reason for testing query. Users are able to select the geographic region (national, HHS region, state, or county), time frames, and reason for testing. Original Code By: Kelly Carey. Adapted to the Rnssp Package by: Gbedegnon Roseric Azondekon. National Syndromic Surveillance Program (NSSP). Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). create_dir: true Detailed Description This template summarizes the types of tests and patient demographics of a user defined reason for testing query.</description></item><item><title>Lab Year Over Year Trends</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/labyoytrend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/labyoytrend/</guid><description>name: lab_yoy_trend fullname: Lab Year Over Year Trends description: &amp;gt;Generates a trend report of testing volume and the percent of tests that are positive for all Lab A LabCategory 2 options in the ESSENCE Laboratory by Results data source. Original Code By: Dylan Johns &amp;amp; Kelly Carey. Adapted to the Rnssp Package by: Gbedegnon Roseric Azondekon. National Syndromic Surveillance Program (NSSP). Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). create_dir: true Detailed Description This template generates a trend report of testing volume and the percent of tests that are positive for all Lab A LabCategory 2 options in the ESSENCE Laboratory by Results data source.</description></item></channel></rss>