<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>list on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/list/</link><description>Recent content in list on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>List available templates</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/usage/listtemplates/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/usage/listtemplates/</guid><description>Rnssp R Markdown templates are being designed and released regularly. All available templates can be explored on the publicly accessible Rnssp RMD templates Github repository.
The Rnssp R package provides various utility functions to easily manage templates. One of those utility functions is the Rnssp::list_templates() function.
First, load the Rnssp R package:
# Load the Rnssp package library(Rnssp) Next, get the current list of available packages:
# List all available templates list_templates() To get a tabular and more detailed view of the available templates, run:</description></item><item><title>Manage templates with Rnssp addins</title><link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/usage/templatemanager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/usage/templatemanager/</guid><description>Starting from Rnssp v. 0.1.0, RStudio users may manage Rnssp R Markdown template with Rnssp Addins.
Launch the addin In RStudio, you can use the Addins menu:
List Available Rnssp templates Users may check the list of all the currently available Rnssp R Markdown templates with the List Rnssp Templates addin:
Or in the R console :
Rnssp:::list_templates() Add/Update Rnssp Templates A unique feature of the Rnssp package is the ability to add R Markdown templates dynamically to an existing installation of the package.</description></item></channel></rss>