<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chief complaint on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</title>
    <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/chief-complaint/</link>
    <description>Recent content in chief complaint on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/tags/chief-complaint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Essence CCDD Categories</title>
      <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/essence_ccdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/essence_ccdd/</guid>
      <description>name: essence_ccdd fullname: Essence CCDD Categories Trends description: &amp;gt;This template generates a trend report of Chief Complaint and Discharge Diagnosis (CCDD) Categories between the MMWR weeks containing the dates you choose. You are able to select as many of the CCDD Categories as you would like to generate this report and are able to control for data quality using the Average Weekly DDI% and CoV(HasBeenE) filters. Original Code By: Kelly Carey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Alerts Report</title>
      <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/word_alerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/templates/word_alerts/</guid>
      <description>name: word_alerts fullname: Word Alerts Report description: &amp;gt;The word alerts template summarizes daily chief complaints and discharge diagnosis term alerts for a selected syndrome definition. Original Code By: Michael Sheppard. Adapted to the Rnssp Package by: Gbedegnon Roseric Azondekon. National Syndromic and Surveillance Program (NSSP). Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). create_dir: true  Detailed Description The Word Alerts Report template (word_alerts) summarizes daily chief complaints and discharge diagnosis term alerts for a selected syndrome definition.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
