<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rnssp RMD Templates on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</title>
    <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rnssp RMD Templates on Documentation for Rnssp R Markdown Templates</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Knitting With Parameters</title>
      <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/post/2021-11-06-knitting-with-parameters-using-the-knit-button-within-rstudio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/post/2021-11-06-knitting-with-parameters-using-the-knit-button-within-rstudio/</guid>
      <description>  First, start a new R Markdown file From Template as demonstrated below:  Next, Knit the template With Parameters using the Knit button in your Rstudio IDE:  References: Knitting with parameters
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Logs</title>
      <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/changelogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/changelogs/</guid>
      <description>State Emergency Department template (state_ed_report)   11/16/2021   The State Emergency Department template has been updated. This version has:
  Modified algorithm for trajectory analysis to improve state and county-level trend classifications.
  Improved figure sizing to accommodate the selection of many categories.
  Improved time series visualizations, color palettes.
  Added interactive sparklines to DT table, Improve table formatting.
      6/8/2021   State Emergency Department template available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cdcgov.github.io/Rnssp-rmd-templates/credits/</guid>
      <description>We would like to acknowledge the following persons for their support and contribution:
Documentation Development  Roseric Azondekon  Template Ideas and Development  Aaron Kite-Powell Michael Sheppard Kelly Carey Sara Chronister Roseric Azondekon The National Syndromic Surveillance Program (NSSP) and the NSSP Community of Practice  Tooling  Netlify - Continuous deployment and hosting of this documentation Hugo - The world’s fastest framework for building websites Grav - A Modern Flat-File Content Management System R - An Environment for Statistical Computing RStudio - An Integrated Development Environment for R  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
